

# **Profile**

Passionate and motivated software developer based in Milan with 2 years of professional experience developing with C# and Unity

Interested in all kinds of technologies, in particular

everything regarding Shaders, Videogames, AR/VR/XR, and AI.

I think the best part of our job is to find a new problem to solve and nothing gratifies me the most than doing it.

I've spent 5 years working in the family business to pay for my studies, which's lead me to understand even more how much I love coding and in particular solving problems.

# **Employment History**

### Software Developer (C# - Unity), UpSurgeOn Srl, Milano

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

During my period working for UpSurgeOn as a Software developer on Unity I was able to focus on:

Unity, Online Stores Management, ARCore - ARKit, Shaders, UI, In-Depth Code optimization, Services (Savings, In-App Purchase, News), Database, Online Server API, Camera Behaviours

### Professor of "Shader Basics", The Sign Comics & Arts Academy, Florence

OCTOBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

After my graduation, the academy offered me a 6 months job as a professor to teach new programmers my thesis subject.

It was an incredible experience teaching young game programmers about a subject that I love that much

### Education

# Game Programmer, Event Horizon School / TheSign Comics & Arts Academy . Florence

SEPTEMBER 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2019

Final thesis: Shader (CG-HLSL)

3 Year course with focus on:

C#, C++, Unity, Teamwork, Working with artists and designers, working with other developers, multiplatform

#### Computer Engineering ( Not completed ), University of Pisa, Pisa

SEPTEMBER 2014 - NOVEMBER 2014

I spent 2 years attending courses and exams.

I learned the principles of Programming, OOP, and attended courses of Algorithm and Data Structures, Operating System, Math and Physic

### **Details**

Milan

Italy

+39 3935667302

giacomo vanni@yahoo.it

NATIONALITY

Italian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTI

22/11/1993

Pisa

#### Links

Portfolio with complete projects track

#### Skills

C#

Unit

Shader (CG - HLSL)

C++

Version Control systems (Git)

OOP

HTML-CSS

Working with Designers/Artists

## Languages

Italiar

English

#### **Hobbies**

Videogames of every type, Card games, Tennis, Skiing